

# RUPERT GOBBER SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **PROFILE**

A passionate developer with almost 4 years of experience who likes:

- learn new things every day
- the beautiful code
- software architectures
- well-written documentations
- open-source projects

My education background is mainly on software engineering, software design, distributed systems and software security.

#### CONTACT

rupert.gobber@yahoo.it

www.linkedin.com/in/rupert-gobber-60a1a6136/ for more details

#### AREA OF INTEREST

Blockchain technologies • Distributed systems • Identity management • Self-sovereign identity • Open-source

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **INTERNSHIP - DELTA INFORMATICA S.P.A, ITALY**

APR 2014 - MAY 2014

Work-school alternation provided by my school. During this period I used PHP and SQL databases.

#### **INTERNSHIP - DELTA INFORMATICA S.P.A, ITALY**

APR 2018 - AUG 2018

Internship for the Bachelor thesis. In this period I contributed to the development of a validation system for interactive e-learning simulations based on the PDDL model.

### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER - GFT TECHNOLOGIES, ITALY**

OCT 2018 - PRESENT

I am currently working as software engineer in a co-innovation R&D laboratory between GFT Technologies and the research institute Fondazione Bruno Kessler (FBK). My role requires the design and the development of software components for the Fintech domain on European research projects EIT Digital and H2020. Main activities:

- Design and development of software components for Fintech projects;
- Development of blockchain and self-sovereign identity solutions;
- Development of frontend and backend components of POC and MVP;
- Writing of technical documentation and deliverables.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE**

UNIVERSITY OF TRENTO, ITALY SEPT 2015 - OCT 2018

#### MASTER DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

UNIVERSITY OF TRENTO, ITALY – TRACK: SOFTWARE AND SERVICE ARCHITECTURES
OCT 2018 - MAR 2022

## **KEY SKILLS AND CHARACTERISTICS**

Coding • Software engineering • Software design • Web development • Software security • Problem solving • Passionate about technology • Fan of agile development • First principle thinking • Keen attention to detail • Fan of best practices

#### WHAT I'M FAMILIAR WITH

Node.js • Java Spring • Angular 2+ • Vue.js • REST • Databases • Microservices • Docker • Linux • Keycloak • OAuth • Truffle • Ganache • Solidity • Version control

SHORT TERM GOALS IN 2022: Expand my knowledge and skills, get work experiences outside of Italy